http://www.cgtech.com/privacy.html

Choose a country
Visit our Websites in ...
Russia
You make it, we simulate it.
Call us today! (949) 753-1050
HomeProductsFull Product LineAbout VERICUTLatest VERICUT ReleaseVERICUT Reviewer (Windows)Composite ApplicationsLatest Composites ReleaseComposite Programming (VCP)Composite Simulation (VCS)Force OptimizationDrilling & Fastening (VDAF)SolutionsWhy use VERICUTTestimonialsUser StoriesNewsletterVERICUT ResourcesComposites ResourcesMachine Tool ShowroomsInterface ShowroomsRobotsServicesServices & TrainingTraining ScheduleRegister for TrainingTraining LocationsSchedule Custom TrainingSupportVericut-SupportSystem RequirementsSoftware UpdateRequest LicenseTech TipsFile UploadCompanyAbout CGTechWhy CGTechCareer OpportunitiesContact usPartnersEducational ProgramEvent CalendarVUELatest NewsForum
HomeProductsFull Product LineAbout VERICUTLatest VERICUT ReleaseVERICUT Reviewer (Windows)Composite ApplicationsLatest Composites ReleaseComposite Programming (VCP)Composite Simulation (VCS)Force OptimizationDrilling & Fastening (VDAF)SolutionsWhy use VERICUTTestimonialsUser StoriesNewsletterVERICUT ResourcesComposites ResourcesMachine Tool ShowroomsInterface ShowroomsRobotsServicesServices & TrainingTraining ScheduleRegister for TrainingTraining LocationsSchedule Custom TrainingSupportVericut-SupportSystem RequirementsSoftware UpdateRequest LicenseTech TipsFile UploadCompanyAbout CGTechWhy CGTechCareer OpportunitiesContact usPartnersEducational ProgramEvent CalendarVUELatest NewsForum
Header
Privacy Policy
Last Updated and Effective Date:
March 17, 2020
YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US
This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the policies and practices of CGTech (sometimes referred to as “CGTech,” “us,” “we” or “our”) relating to the information we collect when you use our website (www.cgtech.com) or engage us with respect to our products and services (collectively, “Services”).
This Privacy Policy applies to our Services in the United States.
The creation of this Privacy Policy grows from our fundamental respect for your right to privacy and will serve to guide our relationship with you.
We value the privacy and security of your personal information, which as used herein means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.
As such, we take complying with data privacy and security laws seriously.
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide you with a description of our personal information collection, use, and disclosure practices.
If you provided us with your personal information, or we obtain personal information about you from other sources, we treat your personal information according to this Privacy Policy.
HOW YOU ACCEPT THE TERMS AND UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY
You consent to and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy by expressly accepting the terms of the Privacy Policy or by using our Services.
From time to time, we will update this Privacy Policy as we adopt new practices and procedures related to your personal information.
Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version.
If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Last Updated and Effective Date” above.
THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND THE REASON FOR THE COLLECTION
We collect the following personal information from you when you engage or inquire about our Services, and describe below the reasons why we collect the personal information.
Information You Voluntarily Provide.
When you visit our website or contact us through other means, you may voluntarily provide information about yourself or your organization, including your name, title, company name and identification, email address, phone number, address, website, payment method, class to attend, preferences, product you purchased, device and operating system, and other information you provide related to your inquiry.
We collect this information so that we can provide services related to a new or existing license file, our education program, the VERICUT Reviewer, software updates, onsite or web-based training, a quote for implementation services, technical support, file upload services, registration for our conferences, and a response to your questions or inquires to customer service.
We may also collect personal information you voluntarily provide in person at trade shows or conferences so that we can respond to your inquiries regarding our Services
Information on Message Boards.
Registered users of our VERICUT Users’ Forum may voluntarily provide personal information about themselves and the issue for discussion on the message boards, which are open for public view.
The purpose of this message board is for the VERICUT community to communicate with each other regarding our Services.
Automatically from Website.
When you use our website, we automatically collect information regarding how you use our website, including the time and duration of your visit, the pages that you visit, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, your internet service provider, your operating system and Central Processing Unit (“CPU”) speed, the browser you use and any websites that link you to our website.
We collect this information so that we can improve and monitor use of our website and better understand our users and their preferences.
WHETHER WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHERS
We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
We may, however, share your personal information with services providers who assist us with payment processing and cloud-based software services.
We may also share your personal information if necessary to:
(1) comply with federal, state, or local laws; (2) comply with a civil, criminal, or regulatory inquiry, investigation, subpoena, or summons by federal, state, or local authorities; (3) cooperate with law enforcement agencies concerning conduct or activity that we reasonably and in good faith believe may violate federal, state, or local laws; or (4) exercise or defend legal claims.
Further, we may use and/or share non-personal information with other parties as long as the information has been deidentified or aggregated.
Lastly, we may transfer to a third party personal information as an asset that is part of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or other transaction in which the third party assumes control of all or part of our business.
HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We have implemented and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and exfiltration, theft, or disclosure.
However, no security system is perfect.
We will notify you if there is a breach of our security where required by law or deemed necessary.
RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Your personal information will be retained for the time required to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected and processed, including for the purpose of satisfying legal, professional, contractual, regulatory, accounting or reporting obligations.
CHILDREN
This website is not intended for or directed at children under the age of 13.
In addition, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.
If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, please contact us in writing via email or using our contact information below.
Please include an indication that your request is related to a “COPPA” inquiry.
After taking reasonable steps to verify the authenticity of the request, we will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.
COOKIES
We and our service providers use cookies on this website.
Cookies are small text files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer or other devices.
They are widely used to make websites work or improve the efficiency of a website.
Cookies help with website functionality and user experience because websites can read and write to these text files, enabling us to recognize you, maintain your account login information between visits, and remember important information that will make your use of this website more convenient.
We and our service providers also use cookies to track our users’ use of our website so that we can learn more about our users and their preferences.
DO NOT TRACK NOTICE
Our website currently does not support or respond to Do Not Track requests.
Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.
You can enable or disable Do Not Track through your web browser.
You can find out more information about opting-out of interest-based advertising at:
http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES
Some portions of our website may contain links to other websites on the Internet that are neither under our control nor maintained by us.
Such links do not constitute an endorsement by us of those other websites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith.
You acknowledge that we are providing these links to you only as a convenience, and you agree that we are not responsible for the content of such websites.
Your use of these other linked websites is subject to the respective terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked websites.
SOCIAL MEDIA SHARING FEATURES
This website may offer social media sharing features or other integrated tools, which let you share actions you take on this website with other media, and vice versa.
These features may collect information about your IP address and which pages you are visiting on our website, and they may set a cookie or employ other tracking technologies.
The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the third party that provides the social sharing feature.
Social media sharing features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website.
Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.
For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social media sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that provide these features.
CONTACT US
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us using the information below.
CGTech
9000 Research Drive
Irvine, California
92618-4214
Or info@cgtech.com
ProductsProduct LineAbout VERICUTLatest ReleaseVERICUT ReviewerComposite ApplicationsDrilling & Fastening
SolutionsWhy use VERICUTMachine Tool ShowroomsInterface ShowroomsTestimonialsUser StoriesNewsletterSolutionsRobots
ServicesServices & TrainingTraining ScheduleRegister for TrainingTraining LocationsSchedule Custom TrainingEducational Program
SupportVERICUT SupportSystem RequirementsSoftware UpdateTech TipsFile UploadRequest LicenseForum
CompanyAbout CGTechWhy CGTechLatest NewsPartnersEvent CalendarCareer OpportunitiesVUE
HomeProducts
Full Product LineAbout VERICUTLatest VERICUT ReleaseVERICUT Reviewer (Windows)Composite ApplicationsLatest Composites ReleaseComposite Programming (VCP)Composite Simulation (VCS)Force OptimizationDrilling & Fastening (VDAF)Solutions
Why use VERICUTTestimonialsUser StoriesNewsletterVERICUT ResourcesComposites ResourcesMachine Tool ShowroomsInterface ShowroomsRobotsServices
Services & TrainingTraining ScheduleRegister for TrainingTraining LocationsSchedule Custom TrainingSupport
Vericut-SupportSystem RequirementsSoftware UpdateRequest LicenseTech TipsFile UploadCompany
About CGTechWhy CGTechCareer OpportunitiesContact usPartnersEducational ProgramEvent CalendarVUELatest NewsForum
